allthatsinteresting.com 2018-07-06

# All That Is Interesting's Privacy Policy

Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:

Our Commitment To Privacy  
Third Party Advertising  
The Information We Collect  
How We Use Information  
Choice & Opt-Out  
Our Commitment To Data Security  
How To Access Or Correct Your Information  
How To Contact Us

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit the [NAI Consumer Opt Out site](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

The Information We Collect:

Company uses cookies to make the Web Site easier to use and more useful. When you visit the Web Site our servers send a cookie to your computer. By themselves, cookies do not personally identify you, but instead simply recognize the web browser you are using. If you do not otherwise affirmatively provide PII about yourself to us, either by registering with us, responding to a promotional offer, or filling out a form, you will remain anonymous to Company.

The Way We Use Information:

We may use third-party vendors, including Google, who use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past activity on the Website, including Google Analytics for Display Advertising. The information collected may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity.

Choice & Opt Out

You will be notified when your personal information is proposed to be collected by any third party that is not our agent or service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. To opt-out of third party data collection, please go to the [NAI Consumer Opt Out site](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

We do not access or collect any of your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
